[
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ميناتو』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ميناتو"
  } ,
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『اورتشيمارو 』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "اورتشيمارو"
  },
{
  "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『لــوفـي 』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "لوفي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『مــايــكي 』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "مايكي"
  },
  {
    "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『روبيــن 』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "روبين"
  },
  {
    "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ليـفـاي 』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ليفاي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ميـكاسـا 』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ميكاسا"
    },
    {
      "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『غوجو ساتارو 』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "غوجو ساتارو"
    },
    {
      "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『سوكونا 』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "سوكونا"
    },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『البيغمام』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "البيغمام"
    },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『كايدو』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "كايدو"
  },
  {
    "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『اســـتا』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "استا"
  },
  {
    "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ايــزن』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ايزن"
  },
  {
    "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『سانيــمي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "سانيمي"
  },
  {
    "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『الهاشيرا توميوكا』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "الهاشيرا توميوكا"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『الهاشيرا ميتسوري』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "الهاشيرا ميتسوري"
  },
  {
    "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『سانـجي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "سانجي"
  },
  {
    "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『اوسوب』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "اوسوب"
  },
  {
    "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『شـانـكس』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "شانكس"
  },
  {
    "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ميهـوك』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ميهوك"
  },
  {
    "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『الشيطان موزان』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "الشيطان موزان"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『القمر العلوي اكازا』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "القمر العلوي اكازا"
  },
  {
   "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『هـانكـوك』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "هانكوك"
  },
  { 
    "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『سـاكورا』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ساكورا"
  },
  {
    "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『شــادو』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "شادو"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『الهاشيرا شينوبو』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "الهاشيرا شينوبو"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『القمر العلوي دوما』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "القمر العلوي دوما"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『القمر العلوي ككشيبو』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "القمر العلوي ككشيبو"
  },
  {
 "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『تانجيـرو』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "تانجيرو"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『نيـزوكو』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "نيزوكو"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『الهاشيرا رينجوكو』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "الهاشيرا رينجوكو"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『اوتشيها شيسوي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "اوتشيها شيسوي"
  },
  {
    "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『اوتشيها مادارا』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "اوتشيها مادارا"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『اوتشيها ساسكي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "اوتشيها ساسكي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『اوتشيها ايتاتشي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "اوتشيها ايتاتشي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『اوتشيها اوبيتو』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "اوتشيها اوبيتو"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ملك الدمار باين』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ملك الدمار باين"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『جيرايا』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "جيرايا"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『تسونادي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "تسونادي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ســـاي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ساي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『تــوبي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "توبي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『كــابـوتـو』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "كابوتو"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『الريكاجي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "الريكاجي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『الاكاتسوي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "الاكاتسوي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『غيـتو المزز』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "غيتو المزز"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ميـجـومي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ميجومي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『يــوجي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "يوجي"
},
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『فيجيـتا』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "فيجيتا"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『دانــزو』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "دانزو"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『شيـكامارو』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "شيكامارو"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『لايــت』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "لايت"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『إل』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "إل"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『إن』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "إن"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ديث نوت』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ديث نوت"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『كيــلوا』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "كيلوا"
    },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ون بيس عمك』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ون بيس عمك"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ديمون استير』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ديمون استير"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『دراغون بول』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "دراغون بول"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『هيناتا』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "هيناتا"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ايـــمــا』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ايما"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『دراكـــن』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "دراكن"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『الامبراطور سونغ』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "الامبراطور سونغ"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『مملكه نيفرلاند』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "مملكه نيفرلاند"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『اكـاي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "اكاي"
  },
  {    
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『السيد لوفي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "السيد لوفي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『اوتشيها لوفي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "اوتشيها لوفي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『اوراهارا』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "اوراهارا"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『كورابيكا』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "كورابيكا"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『هيسوكا』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "هيسوكا"
  },
  {
 "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『إيلومي زولديك』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "إيلومي زولديك"
  },
  {   
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『جـون فريكس』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "غون فريكس"
},
{
  "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『جيـن فريكس』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "جين فريكس"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『سـابــو』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "سابو"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ايـــس』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ايس"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『الادميرال كيزارو』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "الادميرال كيزارو"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『الاخميرال اكاينو』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "الاخميرال اكاينو"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『الادميرال فيجيتورا』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "الادميرال فيجيتورا"
  },
  {  
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『الجيـروسي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "الجيروسي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『الزباله تيتش』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "الزباله تيتش"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『الزباله غوكو』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "الزباله غوكو"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『جـوهـــان』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "جوهان"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『بيـــروس』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "بيروس"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『زيـنو』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "زينو"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ميريوم』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ميريوم"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ميناتـو』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ميناتو"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『بيــتو』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "بيتو"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『بــوف』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "بوف"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『يوسكي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "يوسكي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『رينوسـكي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "رينوسكي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『القمر العلوي ميتشيكاتسو』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "القمر العلوي ميتشيكاتسو"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": ""
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『غيــنيـا』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "غينيا"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『الهاشيرا هيمي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "الهاشيرا هيمي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『زينتســو』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "زينتسو"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『كــانــاو』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "كاناو"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『يوتا』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "يوتا"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『كاكاشي سينسي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "كاكاشي سينسي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『يوهان』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "يوهان"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『سايتاما』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "سايتاما"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『اللحيه البيضاء』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "اللحيه البيضاء"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ادوارد نيوجت』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ادوارد نيوجت"
  },
  {
  "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ملك القراصنه 』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ملك القراصنه"
  },
  { 
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『غول دي روجر』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "غول دي روجر"
  }  
]
